And.
OK.
I think let me open the PDF because that
way I know where I am,
what's need to be done.
I think it was.
I think I lost the PDF actually.
And let's go.
To all the same shipments,
all this shipments.
And I think it's this one, right?
Give me one second. OK, that is important.
OK.
I'm sorry, Africa, can you see it?
Yeah, I can see it.
Yeah, sure.
OK.
Like I I did a lot of stuff here and I
don't remember what I've what I've done.
So This is why I need this.
OK.
Uh, yeah,
so this is this is the the only two
things that we're missing right now.
And um.
Oh,
this is a small like features that I
still need to to work on later,
but this is not important.
And then we done all of it, all of this.
Mhm.
I think our last ones is are which date
was on Friday or Thursday, Friday 7/8? OK,
no, it was 31, maybe first.
I think it was Thursday, not Friday.
Yeah, it was Thursday. Then it was, um,
second, right?
2nd.
OK, April one and two. Yeah.
So I don't know if I show you all of this,
but from here to here,
this is already done up until today.
And let's go with the tender tab.
I think that's the most important one.
OK, so you know as as before, click here,
we have tender here and I was trying to
figure out let's see this part first.
So this is so the user knows the context
2.
Right.
of what's inside here, right? Is to see,
hey, what is the shipment about?
Correct shipment ID, yeah.
So we don't need too many details.
Maybe we can put it here for the
disclosing everything, right?
I didn't get that. What is this one? Oh,
you're saying view details. OK,
And.
when you click on this view detail,
you're going to get all these. OK,
Mhm.
one second by shipment,
sell shipment mode, seed equipment. OK,
Mhm.
LTL.
OK, RDD, gross weight, package count,
volume, distance instruction. OK,
order RDD.
Pick up order, pick up date order,
televideate order numbers. OK.
These are the order numbers part of this
shipment. Direct cost, pick up number,
Mhm.
initial pick up, pick up. OK.
Company is so.
Pick up location OK Date when June 24th,
June 25th up to issue pick up OK the
final delivery June 26th.
OK. For one thing, right? Initial pickup,
you have June 24th and then the order
Mhm.
pickup says it is requested delivery date.
OK, that's fine. Cool. Makes sense. Yeah,
Mm-hmm. OK, perfect.
So that part is this part, right?
you need to meet, yeah.
That part is this one, right?
Yeah, the top part, correct.
And this part,
this little part is will be this one,
but I think I simplified a little bit.
Yeah, this is the same. It is just like,
you know, see you don't.
OK.
How do you say you can? Yeah,
you can give a simplified view and then
Yeah.
give it the full view or you can keep.
We can ask them, right.
Do you want to keep the full view all the
time?
Mhm.
Yeah, exactly. You can exactly.
We can ask them if if you need to to see
Right.
Yeah.
everything or some stuff,
because here I think this is more
Right, right.
important things, right? Mode, weight,
blah blah blah.
Correct. Yeah.
OK and here we have the the table.
I still well,
I think it's already finished,
but the only issue here is when we we
switch this tabs.
See you can we are switching the other
the other columns, right?
Yeah,
the first four or five columns needs to
And that is.
be constant, right? The consistent.
I don't know what what are those.
This one.
I like four or five. Which one?
Pick up delivery until pick up or
delivery. You will have it constant,
right? If you go back to my PPT,
Huh.
Yeah.
which one is that?
It's the green ones. Yeah, it's the sorry.
It's this one's right all all the way to
Yeah, the yeah, until the delivery date,
right. So can we either, you know,
delivery.
Uh huh.
give it a color saying all this is going
to be constant and then rest of the ones
Hmm.
is the one that's going to scroll.
Yeah, because here if if we change it,
we don't see it.
Since it's like too small, we need to.
Yeah,
so maybe I just the column width here,
carrier name, right?
You can make it smaller.
Mm.
You don't have to show the full name,
right? When you adjust the columns,
it should wrap.
Mm-hmm. Exactly. We can, we can auto wrap.
If you can, if you can show that,
that's fine. Yeah,
auto wrap things and make it column a
consistent size so that we can do that so
Mhm.
that you can also pick up date.
Also you can wrap it so that the time is
on the second line.
Always the time is on the second line.
First is date and the time and.
What is the what is that central or
eastern?
Mhm.
It's on the 3 digit code is on the you
know second line so that you can adjust
it and get the other columns in place.
So similarly transit time can be like 2
separate transit and time in below so
that you can shrink the column a little.
Mhm.
Little bit right, so that he can get,
he can use it so that those are all
additional features.
But I'm saying this looks good, right? OK,
OK, yes.
Another thing I made is match the
routing option.
standard status with the actions.
So I put the actions here, Jana, right?
OK, what are those actions?
And with the little truck,
those are standard actions,
all the details.
Uh, gender actions cancel. Oh,
you kept the actions here. OK,
so you put all the actions on the right
side. Right, right, right, right.
Yeah,
because it is related to this one exactly
and I put it in color so the user
understands that whenever let let me let
me select another one because this one
doesn't have a lot of colors.
I think this one is better. Oh,
there you go.
Hmm.
So yeah, you can see it here.
So whenever we change this and we put
Got it.
return there,
you see it's changing color and it
Reach in there. Yeah, then it. Yeah, yeah,
yeah.
changed color.
Then it'd say one thing you don't have to
show, but we can tell them, you know,
you cannot have accepted and sent in one
same thing.
OK, I can I can remove that, don't worry,
but we can put cancel right?
Yeah,
so you you say it's you can show that it
is accepted, right?
But you can show that it is like you
Mhm.
cannot send, send, right? Send.
You cannot do send action because one is
already accepted. But when you cancel,
you can select and you can show them if
Mhm.
it is possible for you, right?
Then you can show that.
Exact.
OK, I will be able to send it right?
Something like that. Yeah.
OK, yeah, that's that's a good catch.
That's a good catch.
But this is cool. This is correct. Yeah.
And here we need to also rearrange the
columns, right? Same way. And this,
Yeah, exactly.
don't worry, this will be done fast.
This I just like I'm just waiting for
everything is set.
Before doing this and here and what I
understand about add quote is that here
Mhm.
This is nice. This looks good.
we're creating a new quote right from
outside. So this that that is.
Not new code. Yeah,
say add code is a is a step either to
Uhuh.
override an existing option or introduce
a new carrier to it.
Mhm.
Oh.
Say I have only three if I wanted to
introduce another carrier.
So I would probably I know that OK this
carrier will do it or probably I talked
to him offline and he that carrier said
like OK I can do it.
So you put you give the add code and once
you add code then you can put the carrier
0.
information and you can add a.
Had a details to it I as I showed you in
the other screen, right?
If you recall in the PGI screen or rating
error screen, there was one.
In the BGI screen. Uh, here we don't.
We don't.
Yeah, PGI, yeah, yeah.
Not here the QA thing,
the the one that is already live.
Oh, OK, that is. I think it's still open.
Let me check.
It was.
So many tabs I don't see things here.
Um, OK, let me let me.
I think it's here, this one, right?
Yeah, this one. If you go back,
if you cancel, yeah, click on the error,
it should go back. Go to the rating.
Mhm.
OK.
Nothing is loading.
And we have to.
Yeah, good. Oh,
maybe you're having the same problem.
It is showing the results,
but it's not loading.
Maybe if I,
but you told me you cannot access it
Possession.
right the last time.
Yeah I'm see I'm able to access it but it
is not loading the value I'm getting
always 0.
Mm.
We should ask.
We asked someone last time.
You only did it you you opened it in
incognito mode and then it was able to do
Yeah.
it.
But we should ask to fix the data to to
who? To same person that gave us access,
Yeah.
right? I think it was Priya.
Mm-hmm. Priya, yeah.
OK, give me a second.
Oh.
Let's try one more time if if this if
it's working or not.
But one point is for to add a code,
you need to select an option or directly
add it, right?
There should be two ways to do it. Yeah,
Oh, there you go.
so if you click on this on any of the
shipments, right? Sell shipment.
And yeah.
Send shipment number. Yeah,
if you click on that one,
you have the base rate, currency,
markup currency and then additional
charges. Similarly,
you should have a screen right where you
don't need the base rate. Sorry,
the right side of the table,
Huh.
right AP and the.
Yeah, maybe you can keep it, right?
Maybe they can just see you and replicate
the same screen, right?
And then you should be able to add rows
Mhm.
as well. If you click on the row,
it'll add row, right?
You can add multiple options.
Options means not options. What is that?
Multiple charges, right?
One to stop off charge.
And then.
And they can have driver assistance if
you come down, not, yeah.
So you can put an amount or you can put a
currency for it, right? USD.
Right, so you can put a.
This is too cheap, maybe.
Yeah, if you come down, Scroll down.
If you Scroll down, it's not a number.
It should be something.
If you Scroll down,
there should be something like codes,
yeah.
Oh yeah, there you go.
Yeah, yeah,
it's just some kind of a junk data there.
So it's showing as a number.
You can put like, you know,
ACC or something like that.
You can pick anything.
It'll then have its description there.
OK, and then I can put.
Terminal handling, right. You see, yeah,
you can put an amount.
So that comes up on the right side.
You see that base rate,
Yeah, it calculates.
it gets added to the. Yeah.
So you didn't enter the base rate.
Base rate is required, right?
You need to put a base rate.
Right.
Base rate is something like the minimum
charge that they would need to pay for
the carrier to move the shipment,
so it could be like $1000.
The first line,
first line is the base rate. No, no,
OK. And that is this amount.
first first line is the base rate.
Go up, go up, go up, go up. Yeah, yeah,
the first one you see base.
This one, right?
Oh, I see. OK, here you can put the base,
let's say. Oh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You need to that that.
Yeah,
that is what you need to enter first.
Right,
USD and then you have to put a markup.
Oh, I see.
You then you have to put a markup.
Markup comes on the customer cost.
It doesn't come.
AP is for the carrier cost, right?
This is what the carrier is saying.
But you add a markup because we don't
want her to just give them.
The same value, right. We want,
we need to make some profit. Yeah.
Exactly.
So that is where you put the markup and
you see that markup comes on the second
AR cost.
Yeah, AR total amount, OK.
Right. Yeah.
So it gets added to the base rate on the
AR side,
but here you won't get a markup on the AP
rate, right?
Similarly you then additional charges,
say for example the driver is moving,
they might put some terminal hand
terminal handling charges, right?
It is like you they go to the yard.
For in order to move the container or
move the material,
they would need some charge right?
So they will put a terminal handling
Mhm.
charge.
Then if if say for example they would
need a drop off charge right or stop over
charge.
So you can select a stop over code and
then say like OK this is the charge that
Mhm.
the carrier is going to do.
And you put all these and you save the
code.
Once you save the code here you don't
have a carrier.
That is where you would need to add.
When you add on a code,
you need to put a carrier as a drop down.
So there would be another drop down where
you would select a carrier.
Um.
Right, if you go back to your screen.
Right. You see the SCAC,
SCAC and the carrier name should be there.
So the third, third column,
third column on the table.
Skype of the carrier.
Oh, yeah, this one. OK.
Yeah,
you need to add those two fields in that
quote, right?
So that if you have a add quote you need
to have the you have to select first the
carrier,
then it would populate its carrier's name
and then rest of the all the fields.
Mhm.
What you did in the other screen would
needs to be there here.
And and you and you're gonna have the the
carriers like listed already or?
Make sense?
Yeah,
just like you you did the drop down
selection right to add charges.
Similarly the drop down will have a list
of carriers,
say in charges you have a list of this
OK.
one.
So there'll be a list of carriers and the
user can select whichever carrier is
appropriate for them once they select the
OK.
description of the carrier.
OK.
Will come up on the right side.
OK. And what about these other details?
If we don't need that for add quote,
I'm saying for add quote,
that is how you do it. Once you add,
right? Once you add,
Mm.
it is going to have all these details
populated just you can show for now.
That will be automatic. OK,
that's just for showing.
Right.
Yeah, yeah, just for showing.
OK and it will be listed here, right?
It will be added to the.
Yeah, it'll it'll add as as last line,
separate line in the bottom.
Oh, it's a separate one.
Why it's not going inside to the to the
See say for example.
tendering at automatically?
No, no, no, no.
What I'm trying to say is they can add a
code to an existing carrier.
Say for example the first rank is WARD,
Uh, yeah, mhm.
right? They can override the 742.
11 with the new code.
Mhm.
Right. They can do that.
Suppose they are picking a carrier that
is a SCAC which is not listed here, right?
Then it'll add as a last line.
Mm-hmm.
OK, so we can add news,
new ones and we can modify these ones,
right? OK, good.
Correct exactly.
So you need to give a option to select
the line and then add a quote.
Mm.
Add a quote. Yeah, of course.
And if you need to to create a new one,
you don't need to select anything because
that's that's a new one. OK.
Yeah, click. Click on that. Correct.
Mm.
And as you say, one other thing,
one other detail to add to the quote is
OK.
pickup date and delivery date.
Mhm.
OK.
Pick up date and time.
You have this column, right?
Pick up date and time. These two fields.
Yeah,
You need to put that.
these two fields needs to be added to the
code page, right? 4 fields to be added.
Scack, carrier name,
pick up date and time,
delivery date and time.
All these the user needs to.
Select in order to complete the code.
Perfect. OK, that that's super clear.
I understand it, yeah.
Right. Yeah,
that is four of these fields plus all the
fields in that one.
OK, that's good. And one more thing. Well,
I think that then this is working already.
And one more thing I'd like to know what
do you show here?
The rate details like this,
this just they spread information like.
Is it something similar like cost
allocation the rate details?
OK.
You have the rate details, right?
What you have one is rate details and the
OK.
other one is what you have.
If you click on that, no, no, no.
Uh.
If you click on the one,
the button that you have.
Right. Retender. OK, one second.
One second. Tender action. Retender.
Retender. Mm-hmm. This one. Mm-hmm.
Why do you have it as tender action?
One second. Let me see.
It's here in in the P in the PowerPoint
as well.
Can you pull the PowerPoint two that I
sent to you earlier, right?
Mhm.
Yeah, it's here. Mm-hmm.
Wait, not this one. Where is that?
I'm looking for the file.
I'm not able to locate it.
Would you like me to send it?
No, no, no, no, no. I will find it. OK,
OK, just hold here.
So you will have tender actions, right?
Tender, re tender, cancel,
OK.
Mhm.
decline and accept.
All these are the actions that you see,
right?
Those are the ones that will be available
for each option.
Mm-hmm. But I what I mm-hmm.
Right so when you click on.
OK, when I click on one.
Yeah, you have tender. Yeah,
you have tender actions.
It won't be tender actions called. Oh, OK,
OK, you have tender actions.
And why do you have rate details?
And because this another button here this
one show rate details.
QCA.
OK,
you don't have to have it at the option
level. This is OK. One second,
let me think. Actions, shipment options.
OK, OK, correct. These are options level,
add code and show rate details, correct?
Uh.
You're right, QCA. And yeah, you're right.
Those two are great details, correct.
Yes.
If you go there, if you click on that.
No.
It doesn't do anything right now.
Right.
Yeah, yeah. It showed read read details.
It should show the information that you
have something similar to the cost what
we had, right. Where is that cost cost?
Yeah.
And the cost allocation this one.
Yeah, great details similar to this,
but you can leave it for now, right?
You can say that you can also see great
details.
You don't have to build all those, right?
You can just leave it as saying they
OK.
should. We can explain them, say like, OK,
you should be able to see the great
details for it.
Right. What is the the idea behind this,
right? Say for if you take the last line,
last line is carrier SEFL, correct?
Uh-huh. Yes. Uh huh.
Right.
Say for this you have a AP cost of 188.29.
Yeah, mhm.
Right, right.
So if the user would want to see the
breakdown, that is base rate,
what is my fuel charge? What is my,
Mhm.
you know,
additional charges like what you saw in
the code, right?
They would have a breakdown of all this
188.29, right? That is the AP cost.
Mhm.
Then they should also have the option to
see the AR cost.
What is the cost to which we are selling
the customer?
For that particular option,
are you getting it?
OK.
How to see the idea behind is the AP cost
here is 188.
And.
29 but you don't know the breakdown of it.
Breakdown is each item level details.
Mhm.
Oh.
Yeah, I I remember that. Yeah,
of course this.
We need the breakdown of this. Mm-hmm.
Uh, just like how we have it in the court.
If you go to the court,
Mhm.
go to the other screen.
The the live screen PGI screen.
And.
Oh.
Yeah.
Yeah, you see the breakdown,
right side is all the breakdown, right.
So base rate, THC, right.
This is the breakdown. Yeah.
Here DHC markup.
So this is the information we need to
show for each option level.
Oh yeah, of course.
This exact exact screen is what we need
to show, right? AP amount total,
Of course.
Mhm.
AR amount total.
This is what we need to show there.
OK, I got you now. Yes, that makes sense.
Obviously, obviously makes sense.
Yeah.
At each at each option level.
So if I click on show rate details,
if you go back to your other screen,
right? Yeah,
And.
for for if I click on line #3 and show
rate details, it'll show for 188.29.
If I do the same thing for rank #2,
it'll show for 716.88.
OK, yes,
of course it will be done for this.
The XP, yeah, correct.
It will be done for that.
What will be its equivalent customer cost?
Mhm.
Right.
That is how it is supposed to tell the
Sure.
show rate details and I do not know why
you are having under equipment rate
information.
Under equipment. What do you mean?
Yeah.
Just before AP cost you see equipment.
Uh, Oh my gosh, I'm.
The table AP cost. You have AP cost,
right? Yeah, just one column before.
Epic. Yeah.
Oh, equipment. I think it was here. Oh,
LTL. Yeah, of course. I think it it um,
The equipment you are having rate.
Equipment should not be rate. Yeah, yeah,
yeah.
it was a bug.
I think it switched switched sides. Yeah,
that was my my mistake. I didn't.
Because you have AP.
Yeah, if you can fix that one,
that should be OK, yeah.
Yeah, I will. I will. Yes.
Because here you're not showing AR cost
Yeah.
either. So yeah, OK, yeah,
that that makes sense. This.
Yeah, this is clear. This is good. Yeah.
Why is this showing up? And then.
We have this and also.
And if you go back to the PPT, right,
if you go back to PPT.
Uh huh.
You have the top action shipments, right?
You have routing query and view stops.
Routing query and view stops. Yeah,
this one will be shown here.
Yeah.
Routing, routing query and view stars. OK,
cool, that's it.
And do you want me to show the stops here
as well or you don't need to work?
Yeah, we already have the column, right?
If you click on it, if you go out of it,
we already have the stop tab, right?
Where is that stop? Yeah, the third one,
Exactly here.
third. Yeah, there you have the stop tab.
So user can go there and view it or when
they click on it,
you take take them to that screen or you
bring the screen on top, that's all.
Well.
OK, so it's like it's the same thing,
basically. OK, OK, perfect. What else?
It's the same thing. Yeah,
no change to it.
What else? What else?
Fantastic. This come out well.
Yeah,
it's oh I I my ask my question was what
is this instructions like this is this
check check check box is is just saying
Instruct instruction. See. Yeah.
nothing or you can edit the instructions
you can edit the hazardous not.
Yeah,
you have instruction instruction in one
It's still.
of the tabs, right? If you go back,
if you click outside, right,
Mhm.
Yeah.
you have instructions. You see that? Yeah,
these are, these are the same thing.
Yeah, I remember this, yeah.
It tells you that there is an instruction
for this order.
For the shipment, there is an instruction.
That's why it is checked. That's all.
Yeah, what what I hmm.
Oh, OK, but what I meant was mm-hmm.
Right. It is to tell the user. Yeah,
it is to tell the user, right.
Say for example,
they're talking to a carrier, right?
They need to tell these instructions or
just to tell them saying that these there
are instructions around this.
What I said was.
Mm-hmm.
Put an information box and if you can
list as a pop-up,
if they hover over the information right
eye icon,
it might tell them all the instructions
and they can scroll and they don't have
Mhm.
to go to the instruction tab,
they can view all those there.
OK,
so the enter looks like it's it's kind of
like a a centerpiece in a way, right?
Because it's like everything is can be
can be accessed. Not everything,
but a lot of things can be accessed from
here.
Correct.
And why when you put here the check boxes
then what I want to understand why?
Yeah,
checks check boxes to say that this is a
hazardous good, right?
You cannot ship it like a regular item.
Mhm.
Oh, OK.
It's a hazardous material, right?
So they're either.
So, so mm-hmm. So it's just a mark.
There are special requirements. Yeah,
just for user information, right?
Instruction is you highlight it and say
that, oh, there are instructions.
OK.
Be careful. Say for example,
during the COVID time,
the the drivers needs to wear a mask when
they enter the facility, right?
They there would be special requirements.
Mhm.
At customer end or at the delivery end,
right,
they need to follow that those
instructions. Say for example,
if you're going to a manufacturing site,
you need to wear protective.
You probably have to wear a hard hat or a
productive goggles.
Mm.
Mhm.
Yeah.
Right,
all the instructions that are given in
Mhm.
the other tab, they can just view it here.
But yeah,
I I totally understand now because my my
concern was maybe this this makes
something like why is this checkbox?
Yeah, yeah.
But it's it's fine now.
I understand it now.
Yeah, yeah. And and one thing,
if you go back to the instruction,
Uhhuh.
if you go back to instruction once.
Not here, the other instruction box.
The other instruction box here.
Tab, tab. Yeah.
Do you have an option to edit and add
instructions here?
Uh.
No, we should do it. Yeah,
because we have 4 notes,
Yeah, just just put up. Yeah,
just put a pin icon or something to edit
we don't have four.
Hmm.
at each order level so that they can add
instructions. That's all right.
Because these instructions, yeah, oh.
You don't have to kill them.
Yeah, they cannot edit. They cannot edit.
They can add instructions.
OK.
Because these instructions were created
in the order process, right?
Exactly.
Say for example there are additional
Uh huh.
additional instructions, right?
For each of those orders,
Mhm.
they can add those in each of the order
lines.
Yeah.
I just put a pen mark and say that you
can edit it, right?
Or just show that you can edit and maybe
something you can show in the UI if
possible. It's not so important,
but I'm just telling you that's all.
OK,
but you cannot create new instructions,
right?
No,
I'm saying you cannot edit the
instructions, you can add instructions.
Oh,
you can add instructions from here as
Yeah, you can add instructions,
but you cannot edit an existing
well.
OK.
instruction.
Say already order 49493 M has first
instruction right delivery instruction.
They cannot go and edit the delivery
instruction there the first instruction,
but they can add a fourth instruction.
instruction to that order.
OK, good. Got it now.
I think that's it for tender.
Let's go with the next one.
Let me check the HTML because we only,
we only did one. We only did this.
Um.
OK, the three dot menu actions.
It was.
Yeah,
though I think these are small ones by
shipment and extender.
I prefer carrier fine, right?
Tender by tender by preferred carrier,
correct? Exactly.
Edit and then by shipment.
What is that by shipment?
OK.
You don't need by shipment,
you just say edit because all these are
by shipments.
OK,
so we can say only edit and tender by
refer carrier.
Yeah, you don't need by shipment,
just say edit because your each of those
actions are on a by shipment itself,
right?
Because the first column itself you see
that as a by shipment.
Uh huh.
Right. So you are editing a by shipment,
that's all.
Yeah.
Oh, so when you're editing,
it's not like a quick action to buy the
shipment, something like that.
No, no, it is not a quick action.
I kept it there to say that the edit is
OK, OK.
for the by shipment to illustrate.
That's all.
Uh.
OK, so the is for the.
You don't need that by shipment. Yeah,
you don't need that.
You can just keep edit.
Good.
And then do you need when we can just do
you do you feel we can do something with
this, some action?
No, you don't need to show anything.
That's fine.
Then we can in in they they know that
what are all the things they can edit,
OK.
right?
All these 45 parameters they can edit,
right?
Good.
Yeah,
we don't have to show because we need to
OK.
create a view for the by shipment itself.
Say if I want to view,
say right now it is it is a by shipment,
right? If I want to view the by shipment,
Mhm.
it is spread across multiple different
areas, right? If I click on this.
There is an order related,
there's a product related,
there's a stop related,
there's a tender related,
Mhm.
so it is split across multiple things.
Yeah, like here.
Right.
So so I probably we don't have that
screen yet,
but when we come to that point how the
user would want to edit a by shipment,
right, then we will get to that right.
Otherwise we can just add certain.
Or we or we can ask them as a question.
If you wanted to edit as a by shipment,
do you want to see all these details as
one screen?
OK, good. Um.
Right,
because now it is split across multiple
tabs and multiple information, right?
If you want to edit,
you want to bring all of those into one
screen and tell them, OK,
this is all that information related to
this shipment. Do you want?
What do you want to edit, right?
Give the user the choice to edit.
OK.
That's good. We should.
We should go to the next one then.
Yeah.
Tender tab status aware behavior.
OK,
then the tap is will be the same thing,
Yeah, tenetab is the same thing, yeah.
right? For both for. Yeah, OK.
Yeah, for both.
For both,
but the status is only the difference,
that's all.
The status is different.
Yeah, the tender status will be different.
We talked about it.
And.
Do you remember in if you go to
monitoring,
Yeah.
the tender status will be different and
when you come to shipment exceptions,
the tender status will be different.
Use you see only. Yeah,
if you see your column in the grid, right?
I think I.
Top grid, you have only done right.
The after origin after origin you see the
column.
Yeah, after origin.
Right in the table above. Not here,
not below in the table above. Yeah,
origin.
Yeah.
After origin you have shipment.
Yeah, next column shipment status.
So this will be either done.
Oh, OK. Oh, I saw.
Either done or, yeah,
because it's related to the other one,
Correct. It will be either done or sent.
right? I remember that. Yeah, yeah,
I that or sent. Yeah, I remember that.
I actually did it. Well,
it actually has a third one, right?
Because it can be nothing.
Or that does it doesn't exist.
No, that is the tender status.
What you're saying,
the shipment status will be either done
or sent.
OK, and it's not empty, never like idling.
It can be hold right?
You see you see on the top one it says
Like.
hold if you see all the status if you if
you scroll up, if you scroll up.
Oh, OK.
It can be any of these status.
The shipment status can be monitoring.
You see all those, right? It is on hold,
it is on consolidation, it is on sent,
Mm-hmm.
it is on spot bid, it is on approved.
It can be any of these status.
Proved. OK, I see. Um, but mhm.
Right. And if you go to the right,
if you go to the right,
you will have the tender status.
I believe if you go to the right after
shipment status,
if you go after shipment status,
Um.
do you have anything else?
I don't think so.
I need to fill the the missing data,
the other columns here.
For this, but I think I had it for here.
It's different.
Oh, that's weird. I used to have it.
I don't know what happened.
Yeah, I used to have it.
That's what I was wondering, yeah.
Huh. Yeah, sure. OK, I'm gonna fix this.
Yes, I remember that. That detail though.
I remember we have centered them.
Yeah, the tender status is different.
I sent you a screenshot.
Do you remember what could be the tender
status, right?
Mm-hmm.
What would be as the shipment status?
The shipment status can be only like 4 or
five, but there are like 17 or 8, not 17,
eight or nine.
Attender statuses.
OK, I think you sent me this picture.
Give me a second.
Right.
Mhm.
Correct.
That is an image that I sent you correct.
Thank you.
Here.
Mm.
It was on what was that last call only I
did send you Thursday.
The one that is is from your flow, right?
You created a flow, but yeah,
Yeah.
I remember that. Yeah, it was,
it was already done.
That was one of the first thing that I
did.
Yeah, wait, wait. I'll paste it here.
I got it one second. All right,
Mhm.
I'll paste it in this chat.
You can pull that one.
OK, great.
Because if we go to my desk.
Yeah, I put it in. Add it to this chat.
No, I add it to this chat, yeah.
Yeah, I I I I know,
I I know it's it's already mhm.
Yeah,
the shipment status can be either hold,
review, approved, load, board, spot, bid,
bid, done, right. But the tender status,
all these can be the tender status,
but we talked about remember use only
Yeah.
accept or send.
Cancelled.
Just for example, right? Accept, sent,
declined or a canceled. Only these work.
Mm.
These two, yeah, I remember perfectly.
Yeah. So, yeah, correct. Correct.
That's all.
And it's it's working.
It's that part is working because you
actually also told me that this one
triggers, for example triggers,
Correct. Review or accepted? Done.
Correct.
for example, accepted is done. Uh huh.
That's why you have a shipment status and
a tender status, right?
Yeah. OK.
So here we have a column with tender
status as well, right? Yeah.
Yeah,
you can just add a column with tender
Yeah.
status and do you have options to adjust
the columns?
And yeah, here.
Right.
I still need to finish.
I don't want to do it before finishing
all of this because it's data data
sensible.
OK.
That's the last thing I'm gonna do,
but I need to bring bring my columns back
Right.
OK.
here. I don't know what happened.
And let's go with the next one.
Then their TA status award behavior.
Then their TA identical both anel.
Yeah mm.
This mapping you were referring.
This is the actually thing that we did
this. You can see it accepted. Done.
Cancel declined review.
Correct.
Cancel declined review sent blank.
This is for.
Exactly.
And here.
We have PGR and that was that is empty
now.
Yeah, that is empty. That's fine. Yeah,
that's fine.
Coming soon. Is this OK? OK.
And then?
Row filter tabs,
Hall consolidation center spot made.
She.
Same as exceptions.
Monitor monitoring row filter tabs.
What are the row filter tabs?
Mm.
Hold consolidation sent spot.
Monitoring tabs,
old consolidations and but that's a row
filters, row filters, same message.
Oh, this one. This stops. Sorry,
they're here.
The second column in the second one. Yeah,
you got it right. Yeah, that's the one.
Yeah, this is that is working right now.
Like we have different values here
already and it's filtering.
You can see here it's filtering the.
Yeah.
Yeah, correct.
And then?
Wire exception table tabs to the filter
rows.
Filter badges show real counts of. Yeah,
you told me that the badges need to show
the real numbers, right? Um.
Yeah, correct.
For the exception ones, this one's Mm-hmm.
Yeah, these ones.
So those are also working. I did see that,
yeah.
Yeah, they are working now.
And then missing product fails generator.
OK,
this this was we were missing before the
has my description, the has my number,
all of this.
I think it was for.
Or database.
OK.
What is that?
What is that hazmat description and all
And mode.
those things? I didn't get the point.
All these fields were missing before.
Now they are.
Uh, these are product.
If you go to product tab, yeah, yeah,
Now they are working, yeah.
if you go to product tab.
Product.
Right. These are the ones. So line one,
if you go scroll to the OK, so volume,
hazmat, tire weight, net weight,
hazmat class. Fantastic. That's all right.
Yeah, batch lot number, hazmat class. OK,
that's it.
This is what we need to see there product.
See for product class. OK,
you're saying product class and shipping
class. OK, shipping class.
Maybe information doesn't matter for now.
Flashpoint.
Uh, OK, declared value. That's correct.
Cool,
it has all the information if you go to
the left.
Right. You're going by order, right?
So it has one line, it has three lines,
it has two lines and it has one line.
So there are four orders in this one.
Yeah,
there are four orders here and names are
In the shipment.
Cool. It's nice. Yeah.
And do you have column adjustments here?
matching, right?
I hear we don't have call of adjustments.
Because there are lots of columns, right?
So it's like, OK, we can say that we will,
we will introduce column adjustments and
all those things.
You don't have to add it.
But you know the idea would be to give
Mm-hmm.
column adjustments like whenever you have
a lot of tables like this right
information,
you would probably want to restrict to
Mhm.
few and let the user select.
Yeah.
Add it.
It needs to be something, um, like, uh,
ubiquitous through all of this.
Correct, correct.
We can make it consistent,
Yeah.
but right now for IDEA purposes is fine.
Yeah, uh then.
You told me that TL and FTL are the
majority of the ones that we're showing.
Rights.
The error is rare and yeah,
so in the database.
We don't have that. We don't have, yeah,
we don't have air shipments right now,
right?
So you don't have to show air itself.
OK.
All you can do is TLLTL.
That's all for demo purpose.
OK.
TL it not demos for this wireframe TL and
LTL is enough.
OK, good.
Tender tab and.
The monitoring.
Jana, correct.
The tender tab is identical in both.
That's that's something we've done
already.
Correct.
It's only the status that will change,
right? We talked about it.
The tender will be sent or accepted in
monitoring.
Send are accepted here, right?
Right.
If you're if you're in monitoring tab,
yeah.
If you go to monitoring and then go to
Oh.
tender below, below you have tender,
right? Yeah, in tender. If you see here,
the call in tender status will be either
accepted. You see here accepted.
Yeah.
Um.
Right. So you have either accepted, yeah.
And if you you don't have the tender
Exactly.
status column here next on the top of the
grid in the top next to the shipment
status.
Here. Yeah, we need to put it here. Hmm.
Yeah, yeah.
There you will have only those conditions
what we talked about in the monitoring
tab.
It will be either accepted or it will be
sent.
Accepted or sent in the monitoring and in
the shipments is all of them, right? Oh,
Yeah.
sorry, in the in the exceptions,
in the exceptions. Sorry,
In the shipments, it will be under review,
yeah.
in the exceptions.
In the exceptions, yeah,
in the exceptions, if you if you see here,
everything will be under review.
Under VM but the and their status.
Yeah, if you click on that,
shipment status is not done.
It is not done. It'll all be reviewed.
Review OK.
Right,
everything will be under review because
the user,
the first screen is to tell the user to
review it, right?
The next screen monitoring is like system
Mhm.
is already taking care of all the things,
right? If you remember we talked about it,
these two screens,
the first screen is for user to review
Mm-hmm.
and because the system is not able to.
To take a decision.
That is why it is called shipment
exception screen, right?
The second screen is monitoring because
Mhm.
system is already performing anything but
the user just wants to see what is
happening. They can go to monitoring.
OK.
Mm.
OK, so here we'll be under review.
That's it basically.
Yeah,
all you could just mark all of those
shipment statuses as review.
Hmm, that's.
That's fine,
although it's confusing because here
we're going to have to change it as well,
right? Because.
Yeah, you you will never have accepted.
That's what I'm saying.
You will never have accepted.
Yeah.
We will have only under review.
We will have maybe sent.
Yeah.
No, no, no. You will have either declined,
declined or you know none.
We can.
None of those even tender has started,
right? Or it'll be two declined,
one empty, right?
But you you don't put a accepted there.
OK.
You never are gonna have accepted.
You're gonna have sent though, right?
Correct.
You can have sent.
No,
you cannot have a sent or you can have.
You cannot have accepted.
And so neither accepted, neither sent.
Send correct.
OK, only declined.
Even if you leave blank, yeah, yeah,
decline is fine,
decline cancel and you need you know you
leave always leave the last line or the
last option empty.
OK.
Blank.
Yeah, okay.
Right.
Don't fill it with any any of the tender
status.
Right.
OK, but yeah,
because here we are seeing an exception,
so we need to.
Only sing.
Exactly.
The user needs to work on something
before they could send it to the next
carrier.
Yeah,
the user needs to see what happens here.
Correct.
So whenever the user wants to like,
let's say I am a user and I see
exceptions, right?
So let's go one one more time to be to be
Mhm.
sure we're in exceptions and I select one
of those.
And I go to tender.
I need to see what's going on.
Exactly.
I don't have. Yeah,
let's say I don't have this.
Let's put it in. Let's put it in.
Let's put it here in.
The coin. Yeah,
you see now it's working like I made it.
Yeah, it is always doing send, yeah.
Like I made it work like this,
like it's it's actually automatically
Yeah.
doing it for me.
Yeah, this is say you. Yeah, that's fine.
We can explain it. Yeah, it cancel.
Because if if I say cancel,
if I say cancel,
Just make it cancel. Yeah, leave it sent.
That is fine. Leave it sent. That is fine.
next one is putting its end.
Don't change it.
Don't spend a lot of time because it's
just a mock, right?
Just for understanding purpose.
It is not like exactly.
OK.
And perfect version of how it needs to
work, right?
It's just some idea to the user.
Instead of just explaining by some
thought,
it is better to show them and give them a
mock and idea, right? That is what it is.
So you don't have to be worried about it.
OK.
The only thing that you need to add here
is.
You add the tender status, right?
So you have a shipment status,
Hello.
add a column tender status and for this
for monitoring alone, right? Sorry,
Of course.
for the review alone you need to add a
column called message right if you go to
Uh huh.
PPT.
If you go to my first PPT,
not the second PPT, first PPT.
Oh, things here.
Right. And you go to sheet three. Yeah,
there on the second column, right.
Second sheet attribute list,
you would see message. Not here. Second,
second. Yeah,
if you you will see one called message.
Where is that?
Shipment status validation message, right?
If you go from bottle 123, yeah,
Message.
Oh, there you go.
that is the message that will come up
there, right? You see check date,
Mm.
then it will say review the tender
because it has a check date.
Mhm.
So the user knows that what type of a
message it is and what action they would
Oh, OK.
need to take, right?
Because under the check date
classification there are a couple of
messages, right?
So it could be a pick up date message,
it could be a delivery date message.
It could be like you know there is no
date at all, right? No pickup date,
no delivery date, right?
That is also possible, right?
Mhm.
So all these are possibilities.
So the different messages can appear for
the check date classification.
That is why you need a message column in
that.
So that the user knows instead of instead
of clicking and viewing the details,
Mm-hmm.
they can look into that grid and see oh
this has a check date and check date
message so they can understand saying
what action they would need to perform.
OK.
OK, see uh.
Just introduce those two columns.
We can voice over and get the feedback
right.
Don't don't put yourself in so much of
pressure to complete it all right.
Just add the columns,
Oh, mhm.
put some message and then we will talk to
them and get the feedback.
Yeah, it's fine. It's fine. Don't worry.
I just wanted to know like the the idea,
like one of my bigger questions so far
was the difference between tender in
exceptions and tendering monitoring
because the actions are the same.
You can do both and.
In in in all in both of them, right?
You can for example you can retender here
Right.
and you can retender here as well.
At the beginning I thought retender you
Correct.
can only do when monitoring because you
are already tendered here.
But you can also read under here.
So like my biggest question was, yeah,
exactly that. What is the difference?
And you told me the difference is mostly
on the status here we don't have is it
doesn't make sense to have accepted.
Correct.
Headed.
Right. But makes sense to have sent,
for example. No, not really, right?
No, you can leave it as sent. That's fine,
right? There could be like the the sent,
OK.
but you know there was no message or it
was not able to do perform.
M.
We can voice over that. So that's fine.
You know you leave it as it is.
OK.
And then like because I I don't know for
me,
I think it's important to show this
functionality in the in the demo about
the actions that you can take for tender
inside exceptions.
Because here you're showing the problem,
right? You're showing the problem of hey,
we we have exceptions,
we need to go through it, through it,
through them and I see the tender and I
want to see the list of it of of what
happened to this shipment.
And from here I want to like showcase
what the user does when they see this
this kind of issue right?
When everything is canceled and it's
empty, what it can be done here can it?
Yeah, right. Pretty tender, yeah.
Can eat tender, re tender and.
Returner.
And when it retenders,
like my imagination tells me,
whenever you retender,
you should show the the user that
actually retender it. For example,
if I do retender here, it's a send right?
Is it that that is that correct?
Can be done?
Yeah.
Is that OK for for exceptions for example?
See, you can have accept, decline, cancel.
Yeah, return. That is fine.
You can leave it as it is, right? Again,
as I'm saying,
the actual business rule will be covered.
This is to just give them idea saying
that at the option level I can do
different actions.
OK.
Right. And then, yeah,
then you can say like I can add a quote
Yeah.
and then once I add a quote,
a new line will be created, right?
So a new option is created and then I can
tender to that option.
Mhm.
OK.
Hmm. OK.
Uh, let's go with the next.
But when will I just come out? Well,
it it looks good, right?
ohh Thank you.
At least at a description level,
the way we can talk to them and show them.
I think it is like really nice.
Yeah, thank you.
It's still like the end of the day.
I'm gonna finish the visual details.
It will look actually better.
Like I didn't want to do that from from
the beginning because functionality is
Mhm.
first, right?
Um.
And then.
Replan.
Um.
Yeah, we're we're we scrapped replant.
In the in our readout, yeah. So that's it.
I think that's that's what we have
Yeah, we don't mean, yeah.
covered everything so far.
I still need to do the the don't worry
about this small things and let's I still
need to cover all of this too.
Search and filtering column.
Arrangement.
For that I need to 1st fix the issues
Mhm.
that we talked here today and then and do
the fixing of the database once the
Yeah.
database is fine and it's showing all of
the columns here.
Correct.
Then I can do this too because I'm going
to have a real database and this can make
Yeah.
sense as well. And from there we're done.
Let me send you a link. Huh. Give me.
Cool. Yeah.
Yeah, and one. Yeah, yeah, one one thing.
One thing is about saved search, right?
Tell me.
Mm-hmm.
Do you have saved search?
Yeah, here.
OK. This opens it. OK, that's fine.
And then when they are searching,
do you have an example how it searches,
right.
So just we're not going to say that
that's all it is going. Yeah,
Oh, right now.
order number, you did something, right.
Order number, you put some order number,
then it'll ask you whether you put some
number, then it'll ask you.
Whether it is, yeah, OK,
this we can explain. OK, that's fine.
There's.
This is fine.
OK.
And then here we can.
This is not working.
It's applying the safe search.
Bring the saved searches.
No, no, you have. Yeah,
you cancel this 3-4.
Something is there towards the end, right?
You remove that. Yeah.
And then you do the safe search. No, no,
you remove that. Yeah. No, no, no.
You have 3456, right? Cancel that.
Oh.
Cancel that one.
Now apply the safe search. Select one.
It should filter something, yeah.
Yeah, it's filtering.
Yeah, so this is enough. Yeah,
so this is enough to show them that is OK.
It's filtering OK.
This is OK. See,
the only one thing that I would want is
this all looks fine. We add the column.
I'll tell you which is important.
Mhm.
You can give priority accordingly, right?
Introduce the other columns in the table
right?
You have only an until shipment status.
Introduce other columns,
Uh huh.
Oh.
put a scroll bar to move it across and
view it and then manage column as an
OK.
option.
Mhm.
View, right. If you can add that,
that is nice, right?
Yeah.
The other one is if you go, yeah,
then if you go to the tender,
Mm-hmm. Don't worry, you'll be done.
tender in the bottom, right?
Tender, tender, tender at the bottom.
Yeah, if you can add, if you can add code,
if you can what we talked today,
if you are, if it's possible,
it's not at this one.
If someone can add a code and show that
in the last line item.
Right as a new carrier,
you don't have to edit an existing one,
right?
You just add it as a new one just for
demo purpose, right? Add a new carrier.
If you can do that, it's also nice.
That's all.
These are the requirements for so far.
Yeah.
OK, perfect. Don't worry,
it won't be done.
Thank you. School. Nice.
We'll see how it goes. Hey, welcome.
Thanks to you.
I may be at what time tomorrow is the is
our meeting.
I think it is 10:00, right?
10 or 111030 or 11. One second,
let me see.
Yeah, it's 9:30, I think for me, for you,
10:30 maybe.
Oh, for you 930, it's 10301030 for me.
Yeah, OK,
I will send you this later in the day
today a link so you can access so you can
access this.
For sure, yeah, yeah.
Please do send me the link, yeah.
And then we can maybe correct a little
small details before the also before the
the demo, right? OK.
OK, sure.
OK. I'll be in touch then. Thank you,
Yana.
We'll do that. Yeah. Thank you.
Definitely. Yeah. Thank you. Bye, bye.
Bye bye.
Again. Bye bye.
Thank you. Bye.